#11 "Snow White of the Yasaka Festival"
Hey, Snow White! Are you
taking this seriously?
Class Rep...
Director
Don't call me Class Rep.
Call me The World's Futaba!
Just for now.
Listen up. The show is tomorrow!
We're not the only ones doing "Snow White."
If you keep acting so limp,
we're going to lose to Class A.
B-But I'm doing my best...
Your best isn't enough!
Where did she get an ash tray?
I bet she just wanted to do that.
What are you trying to express here?
Just you waking up?
No! That shouldn't be the extent of it.
And you call yourself the
girl who has her mask?!
Not good. Class Rep, the scenario
you thought up is starting to waver.
I...
I-I'm...
I'm not a girl!
Kojuurou!
The 41st Yasaka Festival
Is About to Begin
Gargle and
Wash Your Hands
Why are girls so scary?
I'm terribly sorry.
N-No, it's my fault.
This costume is finished, so I was
just taking it to the gymnasium.
Tomorrow's the big day, finally.
I'm so excited.
Where are you headed, Kojuurou-san?
O-Oh, I had a quick errand to run.
Please come back soon.
Fujinomiya is always smiling. That's so nice.
She doesn't say anything scary
and doesn't treat me like a girl.
Kojuurou! Where'd you go?
Come on out!
There's pudding for dessert!
Wow, how nice. So this comes with dessert?
Ugh! Gasou Kanetsugu!
You're in the middle of
rehearsal too, aren't you?
Sweets are the best thing
for when you're tired.
R-Right. You'll get fat if
you eat too much, though.
Aki-chan gets really happy when I give
her little chocolates during breaks, too.
Isn't that really cute?
Wh-What?!
Isn't gaining someone's favor all about
doing lots of little things like that?
I mean, trying a wall slam just
because it was in some magazine...
To be honest, it had the opposite effect.
You really have no idea.
Wh-Who's he to be giving
technical advice about love?
He's just a fatty.
Actually, is he really a guy?
Anyway, let's both do our best tomorrow.
Exuding confidence like that... Just wait.
I'm going to win, no matter what.
And I'm going to be the one to dance with
Adagaki Aki at the post-festival party!
Small treats, good.
Wall slam, opposite effect.
The show finally opens tomorrow.
Is everything going okay?
We can't let Makabe win, no matter what.
There's no problem.
I'll take care of things.
Let's do our best tomorrow at the show.
What's the matter, Masa... I mean, Kanetsugu?
Huh? No, it's nothing.
By the way, I saw Makabe-kun today.
D-Don't talk about him.
I-I'm sorry. You're right.
Sorry to put you in a bad mood.
No, I'm sorry for getting irritated
over something like that.
There's no reason for you to apologize.
I just wasn't being considerate.
You truly are kind.
You always have been,
Masamune... I mean, Kanetsugu.
There are food stalls over there.
Welcome.
Always have been, huh?
I know very well that I shouldn't
be in a position to hear that.
I'm sorry, but I've got my own reasons,
princess of the Adagaki family.
Gasou
My family's been poor for years now.
What's being asked of me is to
improve our financial situation.
Adagaki Group
You're the boy who was close
to Aki-sama, aren't you?
I could tell immediately.
You look exactly the same.
Yes...
I can't fail this mission. No matter what.
That Makabe shouldn't be a problem.
My only problem is the real Masamune-kun
who was apparently a bullied fatty.
Is someone talking about me?
It's probably because you're
running dressed like that.
Stop nitpicking about how I train!
Why do you have to expose
yourself for no apparent reason?
You're in the way of my—
See? You've caught a cold.
Mom! Onii-chan's got a cold!
Hey, wait, Chinatsu!
What?!
Maa-kun has a cold?! Are you going to die?!
No! Maa-kun, don't die!
Of course I'm not going to die!
I am the embodiment of health!
Don't put up a death flag like that,
signaling that a main anime
character's about to go away!
41st
41st Yasaka High School Cultural Festival
Hey, where should we go first?
When do we switch shifts?
We're doing a fluffy café!
Fluffy Café
I wonder what'll be the most fun.
Oh, there's no question.
Double Snow White
Double Snow White!
The Cruel Princess versus Kojuurou-kyun!
The theme of this year's Yasaka Festival is
"explosion."
Explode as you aim for first place!
A-Are you okay, Makabe-kun?
I now present to you this year's
first-place prize... Ta-da!
Did you catch a cold?
I'm totally fine. I'm in tip-top shape.
Thank goodness. Let's do our best.
Priority tickets to food stalls!
Right! Let's shut down Class A!
And a refreshing five days off!
That probably wasn't a good idea yesterday.
Onii-chan, stop that.
Come down here. It's dangerous.
Look, Mom! I'm perfectly healthy!
Do you all want to take first place?
To think that would guarantee
I'd catch a cold...
Yeah!
But I don't have time to rest.
Do you want to go to New York?!
This isn't just about the competition
between Class A and Class B.
Yeah!
And now, let the 41st Yasaka Festival begin!
I guess I'll just rest until our class
is up so I can try to get better.
I've caught you, Masamune-sama.
Fujinomiya-san.
If you're going to look around,
why don't we go together?
No, I'm...
I have so many places I want to see.
Let's go, Masamune-sama.
H-Hey!
I wanted to rest until the show!
Nurse's Office
The nurse's office? Why would
we come here of all places?
Come sit down, Masamune-sama.
Um...
When you've been sick as long as I have,
you can tell just by touch
if someone has a fever.
So you knew from the start...
If you're going to rest, getting actual
sleep will help you recover faster.
Sorry...
Personally, I wouldn't mind if you
didn't make it back in time.
Huh?
I mean, if you win, you get to
dance with Aki-sama, right?
At the post-festival party.
Fujinomiya-san...
I'm kidding.
I wouldn't do anything to
betray everyone in Class B.
I can't even tell how serious you are.
But if you do your best and lose,
I wouldn't mind being your dance partner.
You wouldn't mind, huh?
Yes. Because I'd feel sorry for you.
Right. I'll be counting on
you if that happens, then.
Let's hope it doesn't come to that.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to buy something to warm us up.
Please get some rest, Masamune-sama.
Please hurry. There's only
one more hour until the show.
Aki-sama.
Are you finished changing?
There's a lot of room in the chest area.
I see. We'll pad them, then.
Wait, Mari! No! That tickles...
Huh?
Ow... That was mean.
I was just looking for a place to change.
Everywhere else was full.
Where should I go?
The person playing the
old lady selling apples?
What? You know a good spot?
You'll lead me there?
Thanks!
Welcome
Crêpes
Fujinomiya-san likes Makabe-kun, doesn't she?
Please stop by!
But I'd never be able
to be like Makabe-kun...
Please take a look!
I'm starving! What are you going to eat?
I'm gonna eat yakisoba and takoyaki.
I know! What if I start by
changing the way I talk?
It won't be just like Makabe-kun,
but if I just sounded a little manlier...
I need to sound manlier.
Thank you very much!
Fujinomiya-san!
Kojuurou-san?
That seems heavy. I'll hold it for you.
Huh? But...
It's all right.
I'm a manly man, darn tootin'!
Oden
Light Music Club
Concert
H-Huh? I-I'm so sorry.
Kojuurou-san, where were you from again?
Nurse's Office
Masamune-sama, here's some oden...
Masamune-sama?
I need to fully check out
how the enemy's doing first.
Snow White
Though our prince, Masamune-kun,
wins hands down.
Futaba-san!
Fujinomiya-san, what's wrong?
Is it okay for you to run like that?
I'm fine. I didn't cut open
my stomach for nothing.
I-I see.
Has Makabe-kun come this way?
Masamune-kun? No, he hasn't.
Oh, no...
Where could he have gone?
Did something happen?
He's gone.
Masamune-sama isn't anywhere at school.
What the hell? Damn it!
It's no use.
My fever's going up again.
Oh, so you're awake.
Someone help!
Don't try anything funny.
You don't want to ruin your
hot guy reputation, do you?
You're the one who
assaulted me in my sleep.
It was easy.
If you're upset, build up enough muscles
that I can't carry you around by myself.
This girl...
She just nonchalantly picked
a fight about my muscles.
Fujinomiya-san! Did you find him?
No. Did you have any luck, Class Rep?
I couldn't find him anywhere.
He said he was going to rest
until it was his time to go on.
This is confounding!
Maybe he was beamed up
with some cows into a UFO!
I hope they return him after they've
made their modifications to him.
I know, right? Right?
Hey, Kojuurou-kyun!
Any luck?
It's no use. I looked through all the
bathrooms and changing rooms, but...
You struck out, huh?
But something was strange.
Strange?
Yeah. I kept running into people
from Class A everywhere.
Class A?
Welcome.
Kikune-san, how are things going over there?
No problems here.
I think he tried to get away, but
it looks like he's given up for now.
Just make sure you do as I said, Kikune-san.
I know. Leave it to me.
What are you going to do with me?
Nothing.
What?!
You just need to stay put here until
Aki-sama and Kanetsugu finish dancing.
Until the Cruel Princess and
Kanetsugu finish dancing?!
It serves you right.
That's what you get for
making a move on Aki-sama.
She's trying to keep me from the stage.
Does that mean Class A is behind this?
No, I didn't mean...
Class A is also about to
start their show, right?
But they were panicking as if they'd
had some accident or problem.
They seemed really troubled.
Class B has no chance of
winning with Makabe gone.
Now Aki-sama won't be tainted...
What?!
Masa... I mean, Kanetsugu disappeared?
But he was just near the classroom.
But we can't find him at all.
Yoshino, have you seen him?
What about the other dressing
rooms? The bathrooms?
I had the boys go look, but they had no luck.
What should we do? Should
we get a replacement?
That'll never work.
There's no other boy in our class
who can fit into his costume.
This is totally hopeless.
Is he going to disappear at the
most important time again?
Anyway, let's keep looking until it's time.
Yeah!
I let my guard down.
To think that they'd also
have the same plan...
Wow, I didn't know this
quiet little place existed.
I don't think anyone will come around here.
Thanks. You're a lifesav—
Huh?! Hey, open up!
Open the door!
Hey, open the door!
Now I just need to report to Pig's Foot.
He's not answering?
Could it be...
Please... Could you call the doctor?
You'll be fine. Just put some spit on it.
My plan to play up my illness instantly failed.
Just stay put.
After all this, you'd better
stay away from Aki-sama.
You don't have the right to tell me—
I do!
We're Aki-sama's personal guard.
It all started one year ago.
Seriously? We're entering a flashback?
I was in my third year of middle school.
In the dojo, no one stood
a chance against me.
Except for one guy...
Tawarada
Tawarada Masaru, who would always
resort to almost cheating.
Pure Heart, Clear Conscience
That day, Tawarada managed
to win again because he cheated.
After practice, he quickly changed
and went to ask a girl out.
I-I've had my eye on you for so long!
You really thought you could go out
with me without introducing yourself?
Coward.
That was my first experience with Aki-sama.
Ruthless as ever...
She defeated that cheating bastard
without laying a single finger on him.
I thought she was truly the hand of justice!
Huh... And now the personal
guard of that hand of justice
is using this cowardly method?
Wh-What?!
If you wanted to win fair and square,
you wouldn't try to win by
default like this, would you?
I guess you might have a point!
Are you Morontarou, born from a moron?
But this is what Sonoka
and Mari told me to do...
We said we'd defeat you, so I was
going to try to defeat you.
But there's no way that Aki-sama
would actually lose. I mean...
Wh-What should I do?
Hello, Mari? Thank goodness.
I wanted to ask you something.
Huh? What?
Makabe? You want to talk to him?
Huh? Me?
Yeah.
Hello?
Makabe Masamune?
I'm the class rep of Class 2-A,
and a member of Aki-sama's
personal guard, Mizuno Mari.
And what does the honorable
class rep want from me?
Let's declare this match a draw.
Huh?
We'll let you out of there, so why
don't you also release your hostage?
Hostage? What are you—
Could it have been Master?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Wha— Are you trying to play dumb?
Even if something like that happened,
which class is closer to show time?
Our show is in the afternoon.
I'll just wait here until
my friends come. Bye.
Hold it, Makabe Masamune!
In Call
Mizuno Mari
Now, the balance of power has shifted.
We were at a disadvantage,
but now we have checkmate.
Which will lead to a checkmate for my
eventual revenge against Adagaki Aki.
I'm so mad! How dare you try
to take advantage of me?!
Who does he think he is?!
Stupid! Idiot! Piece of shit!
I'll curse your descendants!
Mari! There you are!
Aki-sama!
Let's hurry to the gymnasium.
But did they find Gasou Kanetsugu?
No.
But...
The curtain will still rise.
At this rate, I'll just perform
this even without a prince.
Aki-sama...
I always knew I couldn't rely on any prince.
Since a long, long time ago...
Now we'll just have to see what they do next.
If they don't do anything,
we'll definitely win.
I'm a coward, and I'm finished.
My master is going to let me go.
Huh? It's Mari again.
Message         Mari          Edit
"Leave Makabe there and help
search for Gasou Kanetsugu."
He's gone, too?
R-Really?
Wait a minute...
Did you guys do the same thing?!
Hey! Wait! Calm down!
Who were you calling a coward?!
You tricked me!
He's not here, either.
Honestly, where did our prince go?
Divine punishment!
There he is!
I'm sorry to make you worry.
They seriously locked you up?!
Isn't that awful?! I have
to go complain to Class A!
I don't know the details,
but now that I'm safe, there's
no need to hurry, is there?
Unlike us, they're going to have to withdraw.
Withdraw?
Well, their prince, Gasou
Kanetsugu, is missing, right?
They won't be able to put
on their play like that.
So now that I'm safe, we've basically won.
Wait, you didn't know that yet?
They've already started their play.
What's going on?
If what you said is true, that means
they don't have a prince, right?
Does that mean they
went on without a prince?
What the hell is she thinking?!